ILGWU Local Publications 5780/169
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Local Publications
1914-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/169
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records, publications, organization files.
5512031
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 28, 2009
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 11, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains publications of several locals, joint boards, and departments of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. In addition to periodicals, this collection contains pamphlets, reports, anniversary programs, and other publications from local unions.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States
5512031
- Box: 1, Folder: 27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: We're Glad You're Here., Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Local 22
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Welcome to Our Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Local 22 Art Workshop Exhibition, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: March 8-20, 1948.
  - Item 4: Dressmakers International Ball, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: Jamuary 19, 1935. 2 copies.
- Box: 1, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Our Record, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Author: Local 32
- Box: 1, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Dress Patternmakers Union, Local 31. Second Anniversary Entertainment and Ball, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Author: Local 31
    Notes: February 20, 1937.
- Box: 1, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Thirtieth Anniversary of Locals 26 and 27. 1899-1929, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Author: Local 26-27
    Language: English;Yiddish.
- Box: 1, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: '33-'43: Ten Years of Progress. The Story of the Blouse and Waistmakers' Union., 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Author: Local 25
    Notes: 2 copies. One engraved for Broadus Mitchell, one engraved for Frederick Umhey.
- Box: 1, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Report of the Ladies Waistmakers' Union., 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: 2 copies.
  - Item 2: Report of the Ladies Waistmakers Union Local 25., 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Box: 1, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Report of the Ladies' Waist and Dressmakers' Union Local 25., 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Report of the Ladies' Waist and Dress Makers Union Local 25., 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Barikht fun der Leydis Weyst un Dresmaker Yunion Local 25, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Language: Yiddish.
  - Item 4: Financial Report of the General Strike of the Ladies' Waist and Dress Makers' Union Local 25., 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Box: 1, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Facts Every Member of Local 23, ILGWU Should Know., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: Local 23
    Language: English;Yiddish;Spanish.
  - Item 2: Welcome, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: Local 23-25
    Notes: Photocopy of pamphlet lay-out pages.
    Language: Chinese.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 Facts for You., Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: Booklet of ten flyers, mostly in Chinese.
    Language: English;Chinese.
- Box: 1, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: We're Glad You're Here, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: Second copy.
- Box: 1, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: A Look Back: Pages Out of American Labor's Past, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: May 1950.
- Box: 1, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Local 22 Art Workshop Exhibition, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: March 8-20, 1948. Second copy.
- Box: 1, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Algemeyner un Finantsieler Berikht, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Local 1
  - Item 2: Report. Klouk un Sut Opereytors Yunion Local 1, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Yerlikher Berikht fun der Ektsekuytiv Bord fun Klouk un Sut Opereytors Yunion Local 1, 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Box: 1, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Our Union at Work, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: A Survey of the Activities of Dressmakers Union Local 22, ILGWU, from April, 1935 to April, 1937. 2 copies.
- Box: 1, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Klouk, Skoyrt un Dress Pressers Yunion Local 35., 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Author: Local 35
  - Item 2: Tsehn Yohr Briderlikhe Hilf in Local 32. Relif Komite., 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Box: 1, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Our Union at Work, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Box: 1, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: American Labor Faces the Future., 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: The Labor Movement and the NRA, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Entertainment and Dance, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: February 25, 1933.
- Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration, 1902-1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Local 10
    Notes: October 5, 1952.
- Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report: Activities and Operations, March 1 - December 31, 1939, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Special issue of Justice, March 1, 1940. Activities and Operations
  - Item 2: Dear Sir and Brother, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Isidore Nagler
    Notes: April 1, 1940. Correspondence. Activities and Operations
  - Item 3: Local 10 Forges Ahead, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Activities and Operations. Second copy.
- Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Local 10 Forges Ahead, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Report to the Membership.
- Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Get Wise to Manager Perlmutter, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Campaign Leaflets of the 1939 Election for Local 10 Officers
  - Item 2: To All Miscellaneous Cutters, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Program of the United Independent Cutters League of Local 10, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Support Rank and File and All Other Progressive Candidates, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Cutters Demand New Deal, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Cutters Demand New Deal, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Cloak and Dress Cutters Vote the Rank and File Ticket, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Rank and File Cutter, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Vote Rank and File Ticket, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: An Appeal by the Progressive Cutters League of Local no.10., 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: A Warning to the Cutters of Local 10, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: The Role of the Three Musketeers in Local 10, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: A Program for Restoring Local 10 to Its Members, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: The Cutter: Special Campaign Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Absent-Minded Mr. Perlmutter, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Final Mobilization Meeting, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Joe Yuni, Candidate for Assistant Manager, Exposes Lying Tactics of Stullberg and His Stooges, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Watch Out Cutters, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: The March of the Stooges, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Beware of the Man with the Mask, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: The Sad Case of Mr. Nagler, "The Man Nobody Wants", 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Cutters Trade Union Campaign Committee of One Thousand for the Re-Election of Samuel Perlmutter, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Cutters Trade Union Campaign Committee of One Thousand for the Re-Election of Samuel Perlmutter, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: What the Members of Local 10 Should Know, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Yehrlikher Report Far 1917. Klouk Finishers Yunion, Local 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Local 9
  - Item 2: Algemeyner un Finantsieler Berikht. Klouk Finishers Yunion, Local 9, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Thirty-Fifth Tenth Anniversary. Cloakmakers Union, Local 5, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Local 5
    Notes: Englilsh and Yiddish
- Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 50th Jubilee Souvenir Journal, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cloth cover.
- Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary Souvenir Journal, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Berikht fun der Klouk Opereytors Yunion Local 1, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report. Klouk and Sut Opereytors Yunion Local 1, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Yerlikher Barikht fun der Ektsekutiv Board fun klouk un Sut Opereytors Local 1, 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Report and Financial Statement of the Executive Committee Cloak and Suit Operators' Union Local 1, 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Box: 1, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Labor Stuff, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1939:Sept.)
- Box: 1, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Thirtieth Anniversary, 1907-1937. Cloak Operators Local 56., Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Author: Local 56
    Notes: January 30, 1937.
- Box: 1, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: 25th Anniversary Jubilee of Local 21, ILGWU, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Local 21
    Notes: February 23, 1935.
- Box: 1, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Local 20 Record., 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Local 20
    Notes: February 1971.
- Box: 1, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Joseph Kessler and Local 20 Waterproof Garment Workers Union., Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: 50 Golden Years: Waterproof Garment Workers' Union Local 20, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Box: 1, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Report of the Waterproof Garment Workers Union, Local 20, 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: May 1, 1922. 2 copies.
- Box: 1, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary Celebration. Scranton District Council, ILGWU., 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: May 3, 1941.
- Box: 1, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 30 Yoriger Yubileous, 1905-1935, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Author: Local 17
- Box: 1, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Report fun di Tshildren's klouks un Rifer Meykers Yunion, Local 17, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Box: 1, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Tenth Anniversary. Reefermakers' Union Local no. 17, June 28, 1905-July 3. 1915., Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: 15-Yehriger Yubleaus. Rifer-Makher Yunion Local numer 17. 1905-1920, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Gala Show and Dance, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Local 15
    Notes: February 22, 1941.
- Box: 1, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Fortieth Anniversary, 1906-1946., Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Local 11
    Notes: November 16, 1946. Cloak, Skirt and Dress Pressers' Union, Local 12.
- Box: 1, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Show and Dance, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: Cutters' Local 11. November 15, 1940.
- Box: 1, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Second Anniversary Dance. Corset and Barssiere Workers' Union, Local 32, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: May 8, 1936. For Benefit of Relief Fund.
  - Item 2: Twentieth Annivesary., 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: February 20, 1954. 2 copies.
- Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Cutters' Almanac 1902-1962, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Box: 1, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: And This Is Local 32 ILGWU, Your Union., 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: Y Esta Local 32 ILGWU, Su Union., 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Language: Spanish.
- Box: 1, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Local 48 Salutes ILGWU Golden Jubilee Convention., 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Author: Local 48
- Box: 1, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: 25th Anniversario Libro Ricordo, 1916-1941, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Notes: May 9, 1941. Unione dei Cloakmakers Italiani.
    Language: Italian.
- Box: 1, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Barikht fun Tswey yor Tetikeyt., 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Author: Local 43
    Notes: Cover only.
- Box: 1, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Your Union Guide, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Author: Local 40
    Language: English;Spanish.
  - Item 2: Your Union Guide, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 3: Introducing Local 40, ILGWU., 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 4: Presentamos la Local 40, ILGWU., 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 5: You're In the Family Now: The Local 40 Family, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 6: The Beltmakers: A History of Local 40, ILGWU., Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Notes: Third copy.
- Box: 1, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: The Beltmakers: A History of Local 40, ILGWU., Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 2: Welcome to Local 40, ILGWU, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: Information folder. Includes The Beltmakers (second copy) and Educaitonal Program, 1956-1957 flyer.
- Box: 1, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: At Your Service: Beltmakers' Union Local 40, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Box: 1, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The Adventures of Local 38: The Remarkable Story of the Ladies' Tailors and Custom Dressmakers' Union, Now Twenty Years Old., 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Author: Fannia Cohn
- Box: 1, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: To the Executive Board Local 38, ILGWU, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Author: Local 38
- Box: 1, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Annual Ball and Entertainment., 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Author: Local 36
    Notes: April 1, 1933.
- Box: 1, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Cloak Pressers 35 Annivesary, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: June 17-19, 1938. Oversize on top of other folders in box.
- Box: 1, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Report of the Dressmakers Union of Greater New York, Local 22, 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 1922. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Report fun der dresmaker Yunion fun Greyter Neu-York, Local 22., 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 1922. 2 copies.
- Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Algemeyner un Finantsieler Berikkt fun fer Klouk un Skoyrt Maker Yunion Local 11, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Box: 2, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Souvenir: The Bonnaz Embroidery Worker., 1918; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Local 66
    Notes: December 7, 1918.
  - Item 2: Twenty-Five Years of Local 66, ILGWU, 1913-1938: Ten Years of Service by Leon Hattab., 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: February, 1939.
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the Dress and Waist Pressers' Union, Local 60, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Local 60
- Box: 2, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Local 89 15th Anniversary., 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Author: Local 89
    Notes: 2 cpoies, one white cover, one red cover.
    Language: English;Italian.
- Box: 2, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Rinascenza: Sourvenir Journal., 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: April 26, 1930.
- Box: 2, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: 30th Anniversary Banquet Souvenir Journal for the Los Angeles Cutters Local 84 Welfare Fund., 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Local 84
    Notes: November 17, 1962.
- Box: 2, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Survey of Health and Welfare Fund of Local 66, New York City., 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: January 31, 1977.
- Box: 2, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Fight's Just Begun: Fifty Years of Local 66, 1913-1963, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Box: 2, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What Every Member Should Know About His Rights, Privileges and Duties., 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: What Every Member Should Know About His Benefits, Rights and Duties in the Union., 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Box: 2, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Spirit of 89: Thirtieth Anniversary, Italian Dressmakers' Union Local 89, ILGWU, AFL, and Testimonial to Luigi Antonini, 1919-1949., Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Notes: November 11, 1949.
- Box: 2, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Tenth Anniversary Souvenir Journal., 1923; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: May 1. 1923. 2 copies, one hard bound.
- Box: 2, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Installation Ceremonies: Italian Dressmakers Union, Local 89., 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: March 28, 1953.
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 30th Anniversary Jubilee, Local 64, Cloak Buttonhole Makers' Union, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Local 64
    Notes: October 21, 1939.
  - Item 2: 40th Anniversary, Local 64, Cloak Buttonhole Makers Union., 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: November 26, 1949.
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 1909-1959, Fifty Years., Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Local 62
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bienvenida a la Local 62, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 40th Anniversary of Local 62, Undergarment and Negligee Workers Union, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 16-18, 1949.
  - Item 2: Fiftieth Birthday Party in Honor of Louis Stulberg, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 28, 1951.
  - Item 3: Testimonial Dinner Tendered to Samuel Shore by the White Goods Workers' Union, Local 62., 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: February 1, 1936. 2 copies.
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Dress Shipping Clerks: A Member of the ILGWU Family, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Local 60- A
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Pressers: Pioneers Forging Ahead., 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: 3 copies.
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 4th Anniversary Celebration., 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the Dress and Waist Pressers' Union, Local 60., 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Box: 2, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Twenty-Five Year of Local 66, ILGWU, 1913-1938: Ten Years of Service by Leon Hattab., 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: February, 1939. Second copy.
- Box: 2, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Author: Harry Greenberg
  - Item 2: This Is Worth Fighting For: Annual Report for 1942, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Life, Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness: Annual Report for 1943., Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Annual Report., 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: Second and third copies.
- Box: 2, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Moving Forward Together: A 3-Year Progress Report., 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Author: Local 99
  - Item 2: 5 Years of Progress and More to Come: A Report on Local 99's Past Achievements and Future Goals., 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Box: 2, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Meet Your Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Local 99 Handbook., Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Box: 2, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: 99 Goes to War., Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: 99 Letters Tell the Story., Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Year Book: 2nd Anniversary Celebratoin and Installation of Officers., 1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Notes: May 15, 1942.
- Box: 2, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: It's Your Union: Use It., 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: January 1, 1967.
- Box: 2, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)